Paul A. W. Wallace Papers 1895-1940 Mss.Ms.Coll.64b
American Philosophical Society
- Series III. Graphics, 1885-1964; 7 items
  - Tehanetorens -- Tehanetorens (Ray Fadden) and others at Conrad Weiser's grave, 1955; 4 items
  - Tehanetorens -- Tehanetorens and sons. (From folder Tehanetorens #4), 1964; 3 items
  - Tehanetorens -- Visit, 23 November 1962, 11 items
  - Tehanetorens -- Visit, 23 November 1962, 11 items
  - Tehanetorens -- Weiser, Conrad. Tehanetorens and boys at Conrad Weiser's grave., 1955
  - Tehanetorens -- Weiser, Conrad. Tehanetorens and boys at Conrad Weiser's grave., 1955
  - Tehanetorens -- Weiser, Conrad. Tehanetorens and boys at Conrad Weiser's grave., 1955; 9 items